Guide to the Carla Stellweg Papers M1752
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2. Gallery Shows, Curatorial Work and Other Professional Activities
  - Angel Lopez: gallery assistant notes, 1990-1996 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Alfonso Pons, 1990-1997 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Stellweg Gallery invoices, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Stellweg Gallery invoices, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Mexican Fine Arts, Chicago, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - J. Vermeer Gallery, Paris, 1991-1993 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Ramis Barquet, etc., 1991-1994 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - M. Ibarra, Paris, 1991-1995 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Partner, K. Rymer, Milagros Gallery, 1991-1996 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Zocalo Gallery accounting, 1992-1994 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Invoices, sales, etc., 1992 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Fleisher Gallery: Ollman, Palacios, 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - K. Mercier-Brent Gallery, Texas, 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - A. Gallo-Colunga, Guadalajara, 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Alejandro Colunga artist folder (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - M. Dinkelman, B'way Space Gallery, 1992-1995 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - S. Throckmorton collaboration, 1992-1996 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Various signage/ads, 1992-1996 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Bronx Museum, 1992-1996 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Stellweg notebooks, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Notebook: gallery, slides on loan, 1993-1997 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Notebook: gallery, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Appointment book, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Dela Cruz collection, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Llewellyn Gallery, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Living Rites, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Invoices: income, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - I. Garza - Capelon, Monterrey, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Invoices: payments, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - J. Lindzon, 1993-1994 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Herman Waller Gallery, 1993-1995 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - J. Drexel - Lam sale, 1993-1995 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Consignments, 1993-1996 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - A Shadow Born of Earth, 1993-1996 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - L. Caballero, secondary market, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Gallery donation to non-profits, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Invoices: payments, income, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Portocarrero, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Colunga - De Gooyer, 1994-1999 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Invoices: payments, income, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Invoices: payments, income, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Santa Barbara Point Counterpoint Show, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - P. Phelps Cisneros Collection, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Invoices, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Art Table, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Sale: D. Rivera, Barbara de Vorzon, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Galerie L. Durand, Paris, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Other consignments, 1996-1997 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Rivera-Gelman portrait, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Kalkunte sale, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Gallery invoices, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - J. P. Morgan: sales, 1997-1999 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Narbona-Capelan purchase, 1996-1997 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Pending, business, 1997-2000 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Stellweg Gallery financial, 1997-1999 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Sotheby's Sale, Vargas, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Sales related, post gallery, 2003-2004 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Louis C. Morton Casa de Subastas (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - "97 Kwangju Biennale" (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - The Buhl Collection 2008 calendar (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Stellweg: stationary and business cards (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - The Drawing Society, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Accounts, 1981-1983 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Museo de Monterrey (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - M. J. Jacobs Artists Books, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - CAA L.A. Women Artists Book Presentation, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Yishai Jusidman, Baja Tratamiento (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Yishai Jusidman: gallery shows (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Bedia re. Cuba, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Gabriel Orozco, "Bride of the Sun", 1990-1993 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Alicia Barney, "Bride of the Sun", 1992 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Cecilia Vicuna, "Bride of the Sun" (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Gil de Montes, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Krasdale Lehman College photo loan, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Salinas de Gortari exhibit, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Arte en Colubia internacional, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - "Uncommon Ground," production, curatorial, etc. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - "Uncommon Ground," catalog (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Katz re. "Uncommon Ground", 1990-1992 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Clippings related to shows, 1993-1995 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Enfocando, Mexico, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Museo de las Artes, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Enfocando Mexico, research, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Women related (ideas that mattered and matter) (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - "Coming out of Mexico" proposal, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Lola A. Bravo exhibit, 1992-1994 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Ava Vargas - Tina Modotti portfolio/show, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Beyond Loss: Art in Era of Aids, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Connecticut show, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Art Pravda show, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Living Rites, Les Levine show, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Pequeno formato latinoamericano, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Marrozzini Gallery collaboration, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Marrozzini insurance, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Rupert Garcia catalog, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - "Babies," proposal, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Photo exhibit gallery, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Proposal show, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Connecticut show, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Dialogues de la Paix: correspondence, contracts, loans, etc., 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Dialogues de la Paix (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - American Society C.S. Gallery lender, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Dialogues de la Paix, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Curatorial idea proposal, "Queer" Show, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - White Columns, Brasil, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Acts of Obsession, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Miami-Dade show, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Rutgers-Yeshiva Jewish presence show, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Press related to Artes Visuales, 1960-1979 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Banco de Comercio presentation (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Expo '67, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Austin Symposium, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - International Encounter on Video, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Latin American Bienaze, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Les Levine Artes Visuales, 1979-1982 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Prep A.V. 23 Los Grupos, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Edit. "Inventory of C. Stellweg Los Setentas" for A.V. or Siempre Monsivais, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Zora (Gallery) first showed Nueva Presencial in Los Angeles, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - C.S. Banamex NY Show, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Image of Mex press and P.R., 1980 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Banamex N.Y. show, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1980s (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Prep Mex artists, 1979-1982 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - [A.V.] Mex artists, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Editorial planning, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Proposal for Polaroid-based art show, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - C. Moser (article A. Visual chicano issue), 1980 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Canada "Mex show" consulation, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Caracas, other projects, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Project- Lecture Univ. of Colorado, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Mex artists books, 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate show info Backdrop "1970's", 1980 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Austin, Tx Mex show proposal, 1981-1983 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Aqui- L.A. text and curatorial, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Letters Artes Visuales, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Post A.V. state correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Demise A.V. NY press, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Artes Visuales subscriptions, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - A.V. correspondence, 1981-1986 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Bourse de L'imaginaire (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Douglas Davis (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - American, Italian, Mexican art, 1979-1989 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Graphica de bolsillo (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Lazaro Blanco and Soma (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Artistas Espanoles, Jaqueline Maggi Hollands (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Eva Koch, NoMad (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Roig (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Miro (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Miguel Angel Campano (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Alvarez Plagaro (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Erakusketa (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Victor Mira (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Pintores y escritores Espanoles, 1981-1986 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Victor mira catalog (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Venezia Biennale, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Glass (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Covacevich consult. Polluck PTG, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Gamboa (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Gamboa - Carla, 1978-1990 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Gamboa Int'l Show image of Mexico traveling, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - VIII Festival International de la peinture (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Latin American artists in the U.S. before 1950 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Lice Meksika (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - My review Tamayo book Rizzoli, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Secondary MKT, 1989-1993 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Re: Cuban Show CS Gallery, 1981-1992 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - First Show- LA Agencia, Prep 1st show gallery "La Agencia", 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence Gallery: La Agencia, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Ray Graham III, 1988-1996 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - C.S. Gallery/ La Agencia "Persuasive symbosis", 1989 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Argentine show, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Gallery starter as: "La Agencia" invoices, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Postcards, 1989-1996 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Subway (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Gen'l Graffiti K. Haring Obit- Aids (News), 1990-2004 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Art in America (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - A.C.S.I.N. project, 1982-1986 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Stellweg-Seguy Gallery (stationary), 1983-1985 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Lidro Corp coll. images, 1981-1983 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Lidro Corp coll. INS. related, 1981-1983 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Lidro Corp: Botero Christies Saze, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Kunsthalle show, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Lidro corp coll. Frida K. R. Varo, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Graffiti press: exh amd collectors and general, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Stell-Seg-Gall exh and collections/graffiti-press, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Soriano Coll-Blade, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Soul Catchers exhibition, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Soul Catchers press, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Soul Catchers slides (Box 91, Folder 43)
  - Soul Catchers: slides and photographs, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Stell-Seg Gallery, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Rammellzee (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Rammellzee Black and White prints, exhibition, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Rammellzee Stell. Seg Gall (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Kentisa exhibition, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Secondary Market graffiti, Picasso, Cont. art, international, 1985-1990 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Untitled, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Maran (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Museum Boymans-van Beuningen, Rotterdam, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Brochure Graffiti artists Liverpool Gallery (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Exhibition catalog graffiti artist quick (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Arte di Frontiera (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - A different climate (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Rooted Visions Mexican Art Today (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Revista de la universidad de Mexico, 1984 Apr (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Involvement (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Encuentro de ceramistas contemporaneos de America latina (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Mocha (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Abstract visions (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - The mining town of Morococha (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Tradition/Innovation in Latin American art (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Current arrivals (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - The War Series, Julio de Diego (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Bach's Goldberg Variations, Elena Presser, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - The Latin American Graphic Arts Biennial, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Signs of transition: 80's art from Cuba (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - 3rd Latin American Graphic Arts Biennial, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Juxtaposing perceptions (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Rocio Maldonano (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Jorge Tacla, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Colombian artists in New York (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - East to west contemporary Latin American artists (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Paper Visions VI (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - House of spirit memories of ancestors (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Geometry Magnet (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Mocha News (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Julio Alpuy (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Roger Welch correspondence (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - New directions: Mexican women artists (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Artextreme, Winter, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Various Shifra Golman, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Bruno Andrade "Abstract Visions" MOCHA, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Clippings (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - MOCHA Decade show, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - MOCHA program exhibits curatorial, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - A. Dias-MOCHA slides, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - N. Peraza/Draft, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - J. Baca Project MOCHA, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - German Venegas (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Rooted Visions: MOCHA extra visuals, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Rooted Visions slides (Box 91, Folder 42)
  - Rooted Visions: MOCHA artists slides, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Press Rooted Visions: MOCHA, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - MOCHA Project Border show research, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Monica Mayer, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Rooted Visions MOCHA C.S. curated, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - MOCHA, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Cuba show project, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - The Latin American Spirit press kit (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - The Latin American Spirit Art and Artists in the U.S. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Texts versions (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Artists not included (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - G. Sepilveda Grupo Alfa, 1982-1983 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - M. De Juan-Alfa, Vesti Corp-R. White, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Homero Espinoza, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - GZLZ VLLOA sales, 1984-1987 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Lodge Rivera-Frida, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Charlot-S. Sofris, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Sec. MKT: sales and info and correspondence, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Various L.A. secondary market, 1989-1996 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Siqueirus-Zablu-Dovsy Coll., 1989 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Rivera 2nd market, 1990s (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Non L.A. Artists 2nd market, 1980-1990s (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Other Latino art 2nd market, 1990s (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - M. Herrera correspondence secondary market, 1992-1996 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - C.S. Gallery, 1994-1997 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Mexico: business secondary market, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Rivera-Angustias Spain, 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Other Latin American 2nd market, 1980-1990s (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Documenta and Muenster research etc., 1997 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Gallery supplies etc. (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Met-Splendors related, 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Bizarre-odd correspondence, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - J.P. Morgan, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Cathy de Zeghar: agreements, forms, correspondence (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Cathy de Zeghar: agreements, forms, correspondence (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Cathy de Zeghar: agreements, forms, correspondence (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - "La Negra Nocha," contract, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - [Il As Newsletter], 1995-1996 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Various Re: U of Texas (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Seminar receipts info (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller Seminar (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Arte Chicano Cult de Protesta: S. Gorodezky (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Proposals: Carla, Holly, John (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Hispanic press (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Mex. press: media/art (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Simon Marcaan Fiz (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Various research, etc. (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Lucy L. [Lucy Lippard] (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - La Cita Transcultural - Nelly R. et al (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Avant garde + museum exhibit (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - M. Mayer (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Sunil Gupta (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Olivier D. [Debroise] (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Hector Olea (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Dupes Cat's Intar Border, diverse wrks (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - G. Yudice/Nestor (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Through the Path, etc. [Through the Path of Echoes: Contemporary Art in Mexico] (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Manual of Style Latin Am Collection (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Questionnaires: address/notes (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Funding (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Art markets + funding (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Blue Star exhibition invites and calendars, 1998-2001 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Blue Star exhibition invites and calendars, 1998-2001 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - CS agendas from Blue Star, 1998-1999 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - [Agendas from Blue Star], Circa 1999 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - [Agendas from Blue Star], Circa 1999-2000 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - [Agendas from Blue Star], Circa 2000 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - [Agendas from Blue Star], Circa 2001 May-Aug (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - [Agendas], 2007 May-2008 Jun (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - [Yearly appointment book] - San Antonio datebook, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - [Yearly appointment book] - San Antonio datebook, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - [Yearly appointment book] - San Antonio datebook, 2000 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - [Correspondence: cards] (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - [Business card] (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - [Artpace] (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - [Mexico Desconocido, includes correspondence] (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1997-2003 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper articles, 1998-2005 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Americas Society, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Program Committee [Blue Star], 1999 Jul-2000 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Evaluate tools, 1999-2000 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Evaluate tools, 1999-2000 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Brd plan + C.S. [Blue Star Board plan] (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Kathryn Gutierrez, 1999-2001 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Bylaws [Blue Star], 2000-2001 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Education grants, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - "Am I Liable? Responsibilities & Liabilities of Texas Nonprofit Organization Directors" (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - CS pendings, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - R. Silveira (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - [Margaret Leng Tan] (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Art Nexus [with article about Regina Silveria], 1998 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Blue Star stationary (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - [Blue Star resignation] (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Viewfinder (Vaive) Cat. Blue Star Art Space, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - JM [Jewish Museum] file, 2001-2002 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Art in General, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Art in General, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - [Fabian Marcaccio] (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - WBX [White Box] booklet/draft/edit (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - [White Box invitations and ephemera] (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - [White Box invitations and ephemera] (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - WBX [White Box] Board, 2002-2005 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - NYSCA/grant application, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - WBX [White Box] benefit, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - WBX [White Box] curatorial projects, 2003-2008 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - WBX [White Box] grants, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Domestic Arrivals Exhibition, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - WBX [White Box] benefit, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Benefit - Lisa Corrine Davis, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - WBX [White Box] press contacts, 2004-2005 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - WBX [White Box] ben. prep, 2005 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - WBX [White Box] silent ben. prep. (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - CS/Hovorarium, 2006-2008 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - L.A. trip, 2007 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - WBX [White Box] ben. auction, 2007 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - WBX [White Box]-MB ben. auction, 2008 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - WBX [White Box]/FY08 budget, 2008 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - WBX [White Box] jobs descriptions (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - R. Miranda - Chiapas - Quitararco - Paris - Milian - [Solidogo?] - Student Castoriadis and Artes Visuales [Custom?], 1974 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Octavio Paz TA, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - U.S.C. lecture cont. art. (Mexican), 1979 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Lecture Univ. Arizona government and the arts: C.S. tempe, A2, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Editor LAICA Journal - Carla (first ever U.S. mag that did a whole issue on L.A. art, done with NEA critics in residence grant), 1979 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - LAICA Jounral correspondence re edit, travel LA, lectures, etc. (Laica was forerunner of Moca, L.A., CA!), 1978-1980 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - LAICA: correspondence artists, 1979-1980 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Matias Goeritz, 1980s (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - [Arquitectura - Mexico] (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Security Pacific Bank Mex Cont Art Show - L.A., 1981 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Del Mese Fisher Gallery - Switzerland request, 1982 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Recommendation L. Fndo [Luis Fernando] Camino, 1982 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Books int'l request - Europe, 1982 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Karen Cordero art history: research, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Dr. G. Stromberg consult advice, 1983 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Various press Hispanic - Art of [fantas?] Lehman College, 1988-1989 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - New Observations mag - R. Armijo/C. Vicuna, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - NYSCA - Diversity Panel, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - New England Foundation for the Arts, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - NY Council for the Humanities panel list, 1987-1988 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - L.A. exh. Hayward Gallery, London, advice, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Nagoya, Japan museum loan Diego Rivera, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Maria Schneider crit + advise, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Latino: Consultations - Advice, 1989-1990 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Shifra Goldman various (siqueiros, L.A., etc.), 1990-1995 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Juan Acha new magazine ideas + book in Germany - Published?, my text = cannot find 8/08 CS, 1990s (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Aqui y Alla - LA mag - L.A., 1990 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Panel B. Brun, C.S., F. Pellizzi, Lowry Sims, 1990s (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Curare related, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Guggenheim grant ltrs - Recommendations, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Cornell revelations Art of Evanescence Symposium, 1992-1993 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Ltr NY Times: Editor Perot vs. Mex-U.S., 1993 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - "Mexico Through Foreign Eyes" ICP Panel text, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - New School Panel, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Int'l Earth Art Exhibit, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Levi's-Arte Latino community service donation, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - MFA Houston Lecture, Guillermo Kahlo - Fotofest - Etc., 1993 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Artes Visuales + photography references, Martha Davidson, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Berta Sichel Baruch Show College, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Nexus Gallery, advice, Suter Atlanta, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - E. Poniatowska/ICP Lecture, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - E. Hndz - Wife of G. Mosquera - Recommended to do lecture women art in Cuba @ Art in General, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Various panels, symposia, presentations + txts, 1993-1995 (Box 76, Folder 29)